Gloria Ho

Junior Full Stack Developer

Forest Hills, NY (646) 535 - 3215 gloria@gloria-ho.com linkedin.com/in/gloria-ho github.com/gloria-ho gloria-ho.com

Summary

Junior developer with a background in logistics and management able to build a web presence from concept to programming. Self taught basic programming and French while exploring Europe and Canada since 2016.

Technical Skills

Ruby / Ruby on Rails Sass / CSS Git
JavaScript Bootstrap APIs
jQuery HTML5 JSON
Python PostgreSQL / MySQL AJAX

Technical Projects

<u>Travel Tracker</u> Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, User Authentication, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX A simple web application where user can plan and manage trip itineraries and funds with friends.

• Create and manage trips, groups of friends, and funds for each trip.

Book Search Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, User Authentication, JavaScript, API, jQuery, AJAX A book search web application conceived and created as a group project.

User can search, preview, and save books and progress to profile, as well as read/write book reviews.

Admin Panel Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, User Authentication, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX An admin panel for a fictitious school where user can create, view, edit, and delete data.

Restricted access via user authentication.

Ruby, Sinatra, PostgreSQL, User Authentication, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX A full stack Tumblr clone with user management.

• User can read, write, edit, and delete blog entries as well as edit profile information.

Pokedex Website JavaScript, API, jQuery, AJAX, Bootstrap, Sass

A Pokemon trainer website that pulls and displays Pokemon data from an external API.

• SASS based responsive design incorporating jQuery animation and Bootstrap.

Movie Info Website Python, HTML5, CSS

A responsive website that displays movie information and trailers.

Experience

Assistant Manager Binex Line Corp., Fort Lee, NJ

01/2010 - 08/2016

Significantly increased productivity and efficiency by developing new training procedures

Momofuku Restaurant, New York, NY

• Managed import/ sales team of 5 employee as well as accounting (accounts receivable, bank deposits)

Assistant Manager Worldwide Axcess, New York, NY

09/2008 - 12/2009

07/2006 - 08/2008

- Coordinated projects from conception to manufacturing and distribution for VIP accounts including Coty, Estee Lauder, Bacardi, and Warner
- Managed overseas production, proofing, international importing, and distribution of promotional products

Managed schedules, payroll, accounting, and HR

• Assisted in opening new branches

Assistant Manager

Education

New York Code + Design Academy, New York, NYSoftware Engineering Intensive2018Udacity, Udacity.comIntro Into Programming Nanodegree2017LaGuardia Community College, LIC, NY30 Credits / Commercial Photography2005 - 2006